This dataset contains materials from the study "" by Soler-Vidal et al. (2022), aimed at studying the activation patterns in response to speech perception in healthy participants and individuals with schizophrenia, with and without auditory hallucinations. The task has a block design with three experimental conditions:
- Word lists
- Sentence lists
- Reversed speech
A low-level control condition of white noise was also included.

Please note that the first 10 volumes of the task were discarded before the analysis, although the whole sequence is included in this dataset.
Events files start at the time of acquisition of the first volume after discarding the first ten.
Please also note that white noise periods are specified in the events file, but were not modeled in the original publication (and thus acted as an implicit baseline). 

Detailed description of the tasks and analyses performed can be found in the published paper (link). Please cite:

[Add citation]